拯救世界，那又如何
反正它又不会突然消失
I saved a row, even though
I know it won't be taken
我原以为你们不会走
我错得如此离谱
I thought at first you'd never go
I was so mistaken
大家都说，生命总有终点
I was told life won't last forever
但我已超越了那条界线
But I've gone beyond the marker
他会怎么做？
会有何感受？
What's one to do?
How's one to feel?
又何去何从
当他没法打开心胸？
Where's one to go
when their heart won't open?
远在天边
却唾手可及
So far away
Yet so nearby
仿佛谁还在看著
我的一举一动
Feels as if someone's still
watching over me
所以，我希望
So, here's to hoping
如今，我已不想面对
生活的各种惊喜
Nowadays, I pick and choose
my circumstances
我不相信，命运有那
我幻想的第二次机会
I don't believe that fate is up
for giving second chances
如果我没想错，时间永不停歇
If I'm right, time goes on forever
感觉还有好多
值得回忆
Feels like there's so much
to remember
他会怎么做？
会有何感受？
What's one to do?
How's one to feel?
又何去何从
当他没法打开心胸？
Where's one to go
when their heart won't open?
远在天边
却唾手可及
So far away
Yet so nearby
仿佛谁还在看著
我的一举一动
Feels as if someone's still
watching over me
所以，我...
So, here's to...
...紧握著渺小的希望
紧跟著时间的脚步
...holding on to a little faith
keeping up with the present day
好好珍惜
我的这些朋友们
standing well with
the friends I made
同时确保
我不会就此迷路
and making sure
that I don't lose my way
他会怎么做？
会有何感受？
What's one to do?
How's one to feel?
又何去何从
当他没法打开心胸？
Where's one to go
when their heart won't open?
远在天边
却唾手可及
So far away
Yet so nearby
仿佛谁还在看著
我的一举一动
Feels as if someone's still
watching over me
所以，我希望
So, here's to hoping